[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the horse saved and trained by Velvet Brown in the 1944 movie National Velvet?", "correct_answer": "The Pie", "incorrect_answers": ["Berry", "The Apple", "Cherry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Color Purple, Shugs father built and ran the Juke Joint that was located back in the woods.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Denzel Washington and LL Cool J were considered for the role of Blade in the movie trilogy of the same name.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the word \u2018alchemy\u2019 generally believed to mean literally?", "correct_answer": "The art of transformation", "incorrect_answers": ["All in one", "All is possible", "The transfusion of matter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to a study an office desk has nearly 400 times more bacteria than a bathroom toilet.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these Asian rivers does not flow into the Indian Ocean?", "correct_answer": "Saigon", "incorrect_answers": ["Zambezi", "Indus", "Ganges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "My source of income is from an inheritance and the Defense industry. Im worth $6.5 billion and first appeared in comic books in 1939.", "correct_answer": "Bruce Wayne", "incorrect_answers": ["Lex Luther", "Tony Starks", "Peter Parker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A guy orders a drag it through Georgia for his son.  What has he ordered?", "correct_answer": "Cola with chocolate syrup", "incorrect_answers": ["Fried chicken basket", "Chili dog, all the way", "A slice of key lime pie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main symptom of the uncommon blood disorder, known as methemoglobinemia?", "correct_answer": "Bluish complexion of the skin", "incorrect_answers": ["10% greater blood volume than normal", "Abnormally enlarged lungs", "Faster breathing because of lack of haemoglobin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the director of the 1997 thriller movie The Lost World: Jurassic Park?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Tim Burton", "Michael Crichton", "James Cameron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is P.L. Travers most famous literary character?", "correct_answer": "Mary Poppins", "incorrect_answers": ["Frankenstein", "Scrooge", "Scarlett OHara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not among the traditional ingredients used for the making of the popular French dish Tartiflette?", "correct_answer": "Rice", "incorrect_answers": ["Cheese", "Bacon", "Potatoes"]}]